import 'package:english_test/models/entities/answer_question_entity.dart';
import 'package:english_test/models/entities/title_question_entity.dart';
import 'package:english_test/models/enums/question_type.dart';

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleReading1 = [
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "What is the topic of this passage?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R11",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R11",
      answer: "Raising a family of great horned owls",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "The phrase “a resonant hoot” is closest in meaning to___.",
    idTitleQuestion: "R12",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R12",
      answer: "a sound",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title:
        "It can be inferred from the passage that the courtship of great horned owls____.",
    idTitleQuestion: "R13",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R13",
      answer: "is an active process",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "According to the passage, great horned owls_____.",
    idTitleQuestion: "R14",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R14",
      answer: "may inhabit a previously used nest",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title:
        "According to the passage, which of the following is the mother owl's job?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R15",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R15",
      answer: "to sit on the nest",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: 'The phrase "precious charges” refers to_____.',
    idTitleQuestion: "R16",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R16",
      answer: "the eggs",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "According to the passage, young owlets eat everything EXCEPT___.",
    idTitleQuestion: "R17",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R17",
      answer: "nuts and seeds",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: 'The phrase “a resonant hoot” is closest in meaning to___.',
    idTitleQuestion: "R18",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R18",
      answer: "the young birds",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title:
        "What can be inferred from the passage about the adult parents of the young great horned owls?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R19",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R19",
      answer: "They probably don't see their young after November.",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: 'The phrase “a resonant hoot” is closest in meaning to___.',
    idTitleQuestion: "R110",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R110",
      answer: "tired of",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "What is the topic of this passage?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R111",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R111",
      answer: "Getting started on the trip west",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title:
        'All of the following can be inferred from the passage about travel east of the Missouri EXCEPT that it ___.',
    idTitleQuestion: "R112",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R112",
      answer: "was usually by steamboat",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title:
        'The phrase "jump-off point” in the passage is closest in meaning to____.',
    idTitleQuestion: "R113",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R113",
      answer: "a point of departure",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
];

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleReading2 = [
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "What is the topic of this passage?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R11",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R11",
      answer: "Raising a family of great horned owls",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
];

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleReading3 = [
  TitleQuestionEntity(
    title: "What is the topic of this passage?",
    idTitleQuestion: "R11",
    answerQuestionEntity: AnswerQuestionEntity(
      idAnswerQuestion: "R11",
      answer: "Raising a family of great horned owls",
    ),
    questionType: QuestionType.reading,
  ),
];

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleSpeaking1 = [];

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleSpeaking2 = [];

List<TitleQuestionEntity> listTitleSpeaking3 = [];
